<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Nirbhay Modhe</title>
    <link>https://nirbhayjm.github.io/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Nirbhay Modhe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016 Nirbhay Modhe</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nirbhayjm.github.io/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://nirbhayjm.github.io/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nirbhayjm.github.io/home/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me I am a PhD student advised by Prof. Dhruv Batra in the School of Interactive Computing within the College of Computing at Georgia Tech. I graduated from IIT Kanpur in 2017 with a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science, where I worked with Prof. Piyush Rai. My long term goal is to develop algorithms that are capable of intelligent and flexible decision making. I seek to build artificial agents capable of reasoning under uncertainty, learning efficiently from past decisions and plan long-term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://nirbhayjm.github.io/home/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nirbhayjm.github.io/home/news/</guid>
      <description>[Oct,&amp;nbsp;2019] I gave a lecture on Reinforcement Learning in the Deep Learning Fall 2019 course. Slides.   [July,&amp;nbsp;2019] Our recent work on unsupervised sub-goal discovery with intrinsic control is available on arXiv here.   [2018&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp;19] I served as a reviewer for CVPR19, ICLR19 and the TLLLEIB 2018.   [June,&amp;nbsp;2018] Our PyTorch code for VisDial-RL is now live!   [May,&amp;nbsp;2018] I will be interning at SRI International in the Center for Vision Technologies, working on stochastic video prediction for navigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Articles</title>
      <link>https://nirbhayjm.github.io/home/publications_selected/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nirbhayjm.github.io/home/publications_selected/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://nirbhayjm.github.io/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nirbhayjm.github.io/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching Assistant
 Georgia Tech, Fall 2019, CS4803 / CS7643: Deep Learning, by Prof. Dhruv Batra
 Georgia Tech, Fall 2018, CS4803 / CS7643: Deep Learning, by Prof. Dhruv Batra
  Tutor: Held weekly tutorial classes (read: recitations) along with holding TAing duties for:
 IIT Kanpur, Spring 2017, ESC101: Fundamentals of Computer Science, by Prof. Rajat Mittal
 Recorded lecture videos in Hindi (partly mixed with English) jointly with all tutors in order to help students who had difficulty understanding English lectures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://nirbhayjm.github.io/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nirbhayjm.github.io/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>